<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">DermCalc</string>

    <!-- Field labels -->
    <string name="label_full_name">Full name</string>
    <string name="label_date_of_birth">Date of birth</string>
    <string name="label_sex">Sex</string>
    <string name="label_height">Height</string>
    <string name="label_weight">Weight</string>

    <!-- Sex options -->
    <string name="sex_male">Male</string>
    <string name="sex_female">Female</string>
    <string name="sex_other">Other</string>

    <!-- Unit options -->
    <string name="unit_metric">Metric</string>
    <string name="unit_imperial">Imperial</string>
    <string name="unit_kilos">Kilos</string>
    <string name="unit_pounds">Pounds</string>

    <!-- Navigation -->
    <string name="nav_home">Home</string>
    <string name="nav_profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="nav_tools">Tools</string>


    <!-- Onboarding screens -->
    <string name="onboarding_1_title">Welcome to DermCalc</string>
    <string name="onboarding_2_title">Numbers that matter</string>
    <string name="onboarding_2_desc">BMI, BSA, PASI — sounds intimidating, but we\'ll walk you through it.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_3_title">Always with you</string>
    <string name="onboarding_3_desc">Your history, your scores, your progress — right in your pocket.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_4_title">Let\'s get to know you!</string>
    <string name="onboarding_4_desc">A little info goes a long way toward making this truly yours.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_5_title">We require a little more informations</string>
    <string name="onboarding_5_desc">Please provide all the required information to personalize your experience.</string>

    <!-- Buttons -->
    <string name="btn_next">Next</string>
    <string name="btn_start">Start</string>
    <string name="btn_ok" translatable="false">OK</string>
    <string name="btn_cancel">Cancel</string>

    <!-- Pickers -->
    <string name="picker_default_title">Scroll to pick a value</string>
    <string name="picker_title_height">Select height</string>
    <string name="picker_title_weight">Select weight</string>

    <!-- Placeholders -->
    <string name="placeholder_date">DD / MM / YYYY</string>
    <string name="placeholder_height">Click to insert height</string>
    <string name="placeholder_weight">Click to insert weight</string>

    <!-- Accessibility (contentDescription) -->
    <string name="cd_pick_date">Pick date</string>
    <string name="cd_pick_height">Pick height</string>
    <string name="cd_pick_weight">Pick weight</string>

    <!-- Validation: errors -->
    <string name="error_name">Please insert your full legal name.</string>
    <string name="error_date">Please pick a correct date.</string>
    <string name="error_sex">Please specify your gender from those supported.</string>
    <string name="error_height">Please double check your height.</string>
    <string name="error_weight">Please double check your weight.</string>

    <!-- Validation: success / hints -->
    <string name="success_name">Nice to meet you, %s!</string>
    <string name="success_sex">Thank you for sharing.</string>
    <string name="age_display">(%d years old)</string>

    <!-- Height display -->
    <string name="height_display_metric" translatable="false">%d cm</string>
    <string name="height_display_imperial" translatable="false">%1$d ft %2$d in</string>

    <!-- Weight display -->
    <string name="weight_display_metric" translatable="false">%.2f kg</string>
    <string name="weight_display_imperial" translatable="false">%.2f lb</string>

    <string-array name="home_quotes">
        <!-- MEDICINE — PHILOSOPHY & WISDOM -->

        <item>\"First, do no harm.\" — Hippocrates</item>
        <item>\"Let food be thy medicine, and medicine be thy food.\" — Hippocrates</item>
        <item>\"The greatest medicine of all is to teach people how not to need it.\" — Hippocrates</item>
        <item>\"Medicine is not only a science; it is also an art. It does not consist of compounding pills and plasters; it deals with the very processes of life.\" — Paracelsus</item>
        <item>\"The good physician treats the disease; the great physician treats the patient who has the disease.\" — William Osler</item>
        <item>\"The art of medicine consists of amusing the patient while nature cures the disease.\" — Voltaire</item>
        <item>\"An ounce of prevention is worth a pound of cure.\" — Benjamin Franklin</item>
        <item>\"In medicine, as in life, the smallest details make the greatest difference.\" — Unknown</item>

        <!-- SKIN — PHILOSOPHY & AWARENESS -->

        <item>\"The skin is the fingerprint of what is going on inside the body.\" — Dr. Georgiana Donadio</item>
        <item>\"Healthy skin is a reflection of overall wellness.\" — Dr. Howard Murad</item>
        <item>\"The skin is the body\'s largest organ, and yet the most neglected.\" — Unknown</item>
        <item>\"Your skin is a reflection of your overall health — treat it accordingly.\" — Unknown</item>
        <item>\"Listen to your skin. It speaks before the rest of your body does.\" — Unknown</item>
        <item>\"A dermatologist sees what others overlook — the stories written on skin.\" — Unknown</item>
        <item>\"Your skin tone is not a condition to fix — it is a heritage to celebrate.\" — Unknown</item>
        <item>\"The skin has memory. What you do today, your skin will remember in ten years.\" — Unknown</item>

        <!-- DERMATOLOGY — PRACTICAL TIPS -->

        <item>\"Sunscreen is the closest thing we have to a fountain of youth.\" — Dr. Patricia Wexler</item>
        <item>\"SPF every day, rain or shine — UV rays do not take days off.\" — Unknown</item>
        <item>\"UV radiation is the primary driver of premature skin aging. Protect yourself daily, without exception.\" — American Academy of Dermatology</item>
        <item>\"Never ignore a mole that changes shape, color, or size. Early detection of melanoma saves lives.\" — Unknown</item>
        <item>\"Check your skin monthly. Detect changes early — it could save your life.\" — American Academy of Dermatology</item>
        <item>\"Retinoids remain the gold standard in anti-aging dermatology — backed by decades of clinical evidence.\" — Unknown</item>
        <item>\"Gentle cleansing twice daily is the foundation of every effective skincare routine.\" — Unknown</item>
        <item>\"Moisturize, protect, repeat. The holy trinity of skincare.\" — Unknown</item>
        <item>\"A consistent skincare routine is an act of long-term self-respect.\" — Unknown</item>
        <item>\"Never sleep with makeup on. Your skin repairs and regenerates itself overnight — let it.\" — Unknown</item>

        <!-- DERMATOLOGY — LIFESTYLE & HOLISTIC HEALTH -->

        <item>\"Hydration is the secret to glowing skin — drink water, do not just apply it.\" — Unknown</item>
        <item>\"Antioxidants in your diet protect your skin from the inside out. Eat your colours.\" — Unknown</item>
        <item>\"Stress shows on your skin before it shows anywhere else. Managing your mind is managing your complexion.\" — Unknown</item>
        <item>\"Sleep is the best skincare product you will never pay for.\" — Unknown</item>
        <item>\"Smoking ages the skin faster than the sun. No serum can undo what cigarettes do.\" — Unknown</item>
        <item>\"Take care of your skin. It represents you every single day, to everyone you meet.\" — Unknown</item>

    </string-array>
    <string name="nav_home_subtitle">Welcome</string>
    <string name="nav_tools_subtitle">Calculators</string>
    <string name="nav_profile_subtitle">Personal Details</string>
    <string name="btn_back">Go Back</string>
    <string name="profile_measure_preference">Unit of measurement</string>
    <string name="profile_details">Details</string>
</resources>
